royaltyyachts.com 2018-01-10

# Privacy Policy - Royalty Yachts

**Introduction**

1\. Thank you for taking the time to review our Privacy Policy. At times, Royalty Yachts will collect certain personal information about customers and visitors to websites hosted by us. Such information will include both identifiable personal data, as well as non-identifiable personal information. Identifiable personal information will be collected when you complete an online form or sign a charter contract with us. Non-identifiable information is gathered automatically when you visit our website and stored for use in our system.

2\. The purpose of this privacy policy is to explain to customers what types of information we will collect and how that information is used. In most cases, we collect this information to ensure network integrity and that we continue to provide you with the most relevant content and best possible service that suits your needs. In some cases, we are required by law to collect personal information about customers. Except where the law requires otherwise, we undertake to protect the confidentiality of such data.

 **Confidentiality**

3\. Royalty Yachts respects customer privacy and the privacy of those accessing our websites. We undertake to protect the confidentiality of our customers and users including all personal information supplied in the course of contracting with us for services. We undertake not to sell your personal information to third parties for commercial or marketing purposes.

 **Collection of Personal Data**

4\. Royalty Yachts collects personal data about our users when you visit our websites; respond to a customer enquiry form; and through the use of cookie technology.

 **Use of Personal Data**

5\. Royalty Yachts may on occasion use your personal information to contact you about promotional offers; advise you of matters relevant to service provision and in some cases, solicit your feedback. However, Royalty Yachts will provide you with an option within every communication to opt out of receiving any communications of this nature or you can contact us to ensure that you do not receive such promotional information.

6\. Royalty Yachts may log the websites you visit; collect IP addresses and information about your operating system and the type of browser you use for the purposes of network/system administration to audit the use of our site. This data, however, will not be used to identify individual users who will at all times remain anonymous.

7\. Any information Royalty Yachts collects from you through correspondence with us, whether via e-mail, telephonically or by written letter, will only be used to address the matters within that correspondence. If this requires referring such correspondence within Royalty Yachts or to a third party to ensure customer service, your personal information will only be disclosed to the point necessary to address your query or concerns, and will otherwise be kept confidential.

 **Site Linking**

8\. Royalty Yachts’s websites contain many links to sites that belong to third parties uncontrolled by us. Royalty Yachts cannot be held responsible for any use of your personal information arising from you disclosing personal such information on third party sites. Royalty Yachts cannot protect any information you may disclose on these sites and recommends that you review the privacy policy statements of those sites you visit.

 **Reservation of Rights**

9\. Royalty Yachts reserves the right to disclose information about customers where required in good faith, to do so by law or to exercise our legal rights or defend ourselves against legal claims.

10\. Royalty Yachts further reserves the right to share information with law enforcement to investigate or prevent illegal activities being committed over our network.

11\. Royalty Yachts reserves the right to monitor user and network traffic for site security purposes and prevent any unauthorised attempts to tamper with our site or cause damage to our property.

12\. Royalty Yachts reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy or update it. Where a major change is made, customers will be informed by e-mail notification or through a notice on our website. Customers and site visitors bear the responsibility to ensure that they have read the changes or updates as the case may be.

## Your privacy is of the utmost importance!
